const currentQuiz = [
  {
    question: "POST stands for:",
    options: [
      "Power On Self Test",
      "Program Output System Test",
      "Primary OS Test",
      "None"
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Which is volatile memory?",
    options: ["ROM", "Hard Disk", "RAM", "DVD"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Windows is an example of:",
    options: [
      "Application software",
      "System software",
      "Utility software",
      "Antivirus"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "CPU mainly consists of:",
    options: [
      "ALU & CU",
      "RAM & ROM",
      "Monitor & Keyboard",
      "Printer & Scanner"
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "BIOS is stored in:",
    options: [
      "RAM",
      "ROM",
      "Cache",
      "Hard Disk"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Bit stands for:",
    options: [
      "Binary Digit",
      "Byte Integer",
      "Basic Input",
      "None"
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "1 MB equals:",
    options: [
      "1000 KB",
      "1024 KB ",
      "1024 Bytes",
      "100 Bytes"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is an input device?",
    options: [
      "Monitor",
      "Keyboard",
      "Printer",
      "Speaker"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is secondary storage?",
    options: [
      "RAM",
      "Cache",
      "Register",
      "Hard Disk"
    ],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Firmware is stored in:",
    options: [
      "RAM",
      "ROM",
      "CPU",
      "HDD"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Computer works on which number system? ",
    options: [
      "Decimal",
      "Octal",
      "Binary",
      "Hexadecimal"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "OS acts as an interface between:  ",
    options: [
      "User & Hardware",
      "Software & Software",
      "User & User",
      "Internet & User "
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Shortcut to open Task Manager:",
    options: [
      "Ctrl + T",
      "Ctrl + Shift + Esc",
      "Alt + F4",
      "Ctrl + Alt + P"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "File deleted normally goes to: ",
    options: [
      "Control Panel ",
      "Desktop",
      "Recycle Bin",
      "Drive C "
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Ctrl + C is used for: ",
    options: [
      "Cut",
      "Copy",
      "Paste",
      "Close"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Ctrl + X is used for: ",
    options: [
      "Copy",
      "Cut",
      "Paste",
      "Undo"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Shortcut for permanent delete:  ",
    options: [
      "Delete",
      "Ctrl + Delete",
      "Shift + Delete",
      "Alt + Delete"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Windows Explorer is used for: ",
    options: [
      "Internet",
      "File Management",
      "Email",
      "Antivirus"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Extension of executable file: ",
    options: [
      ".docx ",
      ".xlsx",
      ".exe",
      ".pptx "
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Booting means:",
    options: [
      "Shutdown",
      "Restart",
      "Starting computer",
      "Formatting"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Writer is used for: ",
    options: [
      "Calculation",
      "Presentation",
      "Word Processing ",
      "Drawing"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Shortcut to save document:",
    options: [
      "Ctrl + A",
      "Ctrl + S",
      "Ctrl + P",
      "Ctrl + D"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Ctrl + B is for:",
    options: [
      "Bold",
      "Italic",
      "Underline",
      "Break"
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Ctrl + I is for:",
    options: [
      "Indent",
      "Italic",
      "Insert",
      "Index "
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Ctrl + U is for:",
    options: [
      "Uppercase",
      "Undo",
      "Underline",
      "Update"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Header appears at:",
    options: [
      "Bottom",
      "Top",
      "Middle",
      "Margin"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Footer appears at:",
    options: [
      "Bottom",
      "Top",
      "Center",
      "Side"
    ],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Page Break shortcut:",
    options: [
      "Ctrl + B",
      "Ctrl + Enter",
      "Ctrl + Shift",
      "Ctrl + P"
    ],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Spell check shortcut:",
    options: [
      "F2",
      "F5",
      "F7",
      "F9"
    ],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Default file extension of Writer:",
    options: [
      ".doc",
      ".odt ",
      ".txt",
      ".pdf"
    ],
    answer: 1
  }
];
loadQuiz(currentQuiz)
